gamingunion.net 2014-12-16

# Privacy Policy | GamingUnion.net

  * [Home](http://www.gamingunion.net/) /
  * Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. We believe that a strong guarantee of privacy is essential to our success and to your ongoing patronage. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be voluntarily supplied or requested. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website.

## The Way We Use Information

* * *

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses, unless acting under a good faith belief that such action is necessary:

  * Conform to legal requirements imposed on us or to comply with a legal process.
  * Protect and defend Gaming Union Network's rights or property.
  * Enforce the Gaming Union Network Conditions of Use.

## Online Behavioral Advertising (OBA)

* * *

We partner with ValueClick Media to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick Media may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g. visits to this site, responses to ads) during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this "behavioral advertising" practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.
